We can still track down Golda.
Hello, Peter?
The members of the syndicate
are here.
They're going to the spa.
Where's Golda?
You won't tell me?
They went that way!
There they are!
We have to go!
I got something.
Batikang Ganda?
It's a women's clothing
and lifestyle store.
We can get out of here, too.
Just hide!
Go, Joey. Take care.
I'll cover you.
How about you?
I'll meet you at the boarding
house.
One, two, three! You run!
Jin Ho!
Go!
Golda's cousin,
who is the manager,
escaped, Ma'am.
The Korean helped him.
The one we encountered before.
He must have had an idea about
our organization.
You won't realize you're going
to confront him.
I know where to find Golda.
- At Amoroso.
How did you know?
From the logo Golda was wearing
when we saw her.
There's only one store, Joey.
At Amoroso.
I really appreciate that
even though I said some unkind
things to you,
you still wanted to help me.
So thank you, Andrew.
I guess, we'll go to Amoroso.l
Hey!
Hi, Ma'am Golda. Welcome back!
Have a seat, Ma'am.
Oh my, you need to entertain me
because stress eating isn't
working for me anymore.
Maybe I'll try stress dressing
to make myself feel better,
right?
Perfect, Ma'am.
We have a new arrival,
for attention grabber!
I want lthat!
I want something sexy
and sophisticated!
Something that makes the rich
and famous look at me and say...
Who's that?
I want her number.
That's it! I want that!
Ma'am, I know something
that's right for you.
This, Ma'am. Isn't it beautiful?
I want that! That's so cute!
Let me try it.
Okay.
So nice!
Is this Amoroso?
Yeah.
I did some research last night.
This place is huge,
so setting expectations...
I mean, finding Golda
won't be easy.
Where will we start?
Miss?
Yes?
Can you hold this?
It's ugly.
Please change this!
It's not my type!
Here, Ma'am, there's another
one.
- Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- It's beautiful, isn't it?
Wow...
- This, Ma'am, I have a lot.
- Hurry!
I bet it's this one,
the pink one,
the Fuchsia pink one.
Miss...
- Yes, Ma'am?
- Miss, my phone is ringing.
Please get it.
Okay, Ma'am, just wait.
Ma'am, I'll open your bag, okay?
Yes, go!
- Ma'am, here it is.
- Okay, thank you.
Hello, Cous?
Well, it's a good thing you
callelld.
By the way, our exchange point
has been compromised.
But I'll just look for something
else,
and then I'll let you know.
Golda, that's the thing.
They made me confess.
I didn't mean to.
I'm really sorry.
What did you confess?
They're looking for you.
I told them where you were.
I told them you were at Amoroso.
I'm really sorry, Golda.
They already know.
Fine!
Let them come here because they
can't get near me anymore
because I'm about to become
untouchable.
Miss, is there any orange there?
Try this.
This is beautiful!
Can we still find her here?
I hope.
I'll stay here.
I'll be the lookout.
Okay.
Let's go.
Joey, be careful.
We can ask her.
Miss, do you know Golda Briones?
Miss, I'll just get this, Miss.
Wait, I'll choose first.
It looks like it's Golda.
Golda!
You're so slow.
If you have to find every runner
and dealer in Bolagos
to track down Golda, do it!
You're so dramatic, Matias.
Getting all worked up because
of a low-class drug runner.
My god.
I'm sorry,
but I don't want to be
complacent,
especially since someone
else is looking for Golda,
right.
That can bring you down.
Who?
And why would Lisa
be dragged down?
Golda?
Golda? Why are you touching me?
You know this is a dressing
room!
You know I'm getting dressed,
right?
I thought you were someone
else...
Miss, tell him!
Joey?
Hello, Peter?
Wait, don't touch me!
Wait, what's going on
down there?
Well, it's not Golda here.
Look for her downstairs
right away.
We're going downstairs too.
I'll just fix the mess here.
Okay, okay, okay, I'll go.
We were just looking
for someone.
- Fix it, Miss!
- Sorry, sorry.
Miss, scold him!
I'll report it, Miss, okay!
- It's a nuisance!
- Come on, come on.
- Don't touch me!
- Sorry. Sorry.
Excuse me. Come on, come on.
What's wrong, Miss?
Scold them, Miss!
Ma'am, I'm sorry I'll just
give you a discount, Ma'am.
What's with you?
Can't you wait?
- Hello, Peter?
- Joey, Joey, Golda's leaving.
Come here now!
Now!
Boss, wait, wait!
Wait, my shoelace!
Wait?
Hey, step aside.
Joey, hurry up!
What's that?
There's a crazy guy blocking
the way, Ma'am!
Then avoid him!
Peter!
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
It's...
it's the police.
They're also looking for Golda,
remember?
Authorities finding her means
our downfall.
Don't let it drag on.
We have bigger problems
than that.
Look,
our revenue is going down.
We only have Luzon and NCR.
Are we rusty?
Is it because of the compromised
shipments?
We also had some deals canceled
because the client backed out.
Matias,
when was the last time you spoke
to Braganza?
It's been a while since he
formed his own group in VisMin.
Well, guess what?
He's not just working in VisMin.
He also entered Region 4
and Region 5.
That means our clients
are now his.
And I'm sure, he'll follow
the NCR too!
Sir.
Golda.
Godfather!
Wow...
Your guns are driving me crazy,
Godfather.
It's like a coup d'etat.
That's how it should be, hija.
Every day is revolution day.
The only question is,
which side are you on?
Me, I grind between the legal
and the illegal.
That way, when the war
continues,
I'm still the supplier.
I'm still the winner.
You're really brainy, Godfather.
You're full of foolishness.
You know,
I did some digging on your man,
Braganza.
He seems okay.
Come on, Godfather!
Of course, I won't introduce you
to any sloppy clients.
You only deserve the best
of the bestest.
That's what I want from you.
You're a great flatterer.
I know, right?
That's why I convinced you
to let me stay here
in your fancy villa.
That's nothing.
I have to protect the people
that can affect my business.
Didn't you say someone
was looking for you?
How did you find me?
I'm Miguel Delgado's son.
Don't follow me, okay?
They won't be able
to get near me
because I'm about to become
untouchable.
You look worried.
I don't like that.
That's bad for business.
Sorry, Godfather.
Let's forget about them.
No, no, no.
The problem must be solved
before it gets bigger.
Tell me who they are.
I will have my men finish them.
Are there really only two rooms
here?
Why? Are you still choosy?
What are you? Nepo baby?
Nepo baby?
Of course, there are four of us.
Well...
Joey is alone in one room,
and the three of us, you, me,
and Jin Ho, in one room.
I can sleep on the couch.
You see?
You're fussier than Jin Ho.
I'm not fussy.
Of course, I'm only worried
about you.
But if you'll be alone,
then it's good.
Videogames...
Videogames!
What games?
Do you want to play? I'll
prepare, I'll prepare.
What games?
We didn't come here
to play games.
We came here to look for Golda.
Just excited.
Where are we going to look?
I got the license plate number
of the SUV.
I'll work on it right away.
As for me, I won't leave Amoroso
until I find that Golda.
I need her to confess because...
that's the only way
to free Father.
Godfather, you're making me
nervous.
Of course, I'm not worried!
What? They're just small time.
Are you sure?
Yes, of course!
And besides,
the bullets in your gun are
worth more than their lives.
Godfather, you know,
I have good news for you.
I'm 99 percent sure
I can fast-track your deal
with Braganza.
Good, good.
If you fix that on
or before my birthday,
I'll double your cut.
Really, Godfather?
Wow! Thank you so much,
Godfather!
I'll go with that!
So excited!
It's not possible next week,
Andrew.
The client is following up
again.
Wait, can I...
I'll just do what I need
to shoot here.
No, you can't.
They have a technical
requirement.
And then they want you here
on the Tirada Express bus.
Okay, I'll go home.
Okay.
Do you need to leave?
Yes.
I just need to take care
of something for a client, Joey.
I'll be back tomorrow morning.
Okay.
While you're gone,
Peter and I will just go around
with Jin Ho.
Okay, and I'll also take care of
the SUV's license plate number.
Be careful.
Okay.
Andrew...
can I ask you a favor?
Sure, what's that?
Can you visit my father?
Of course.
Thank you.
Okay.
He's still nowhere to be seen.
Even now, I haven't seen
any news about him.
Miguel, maybe you know where
Diego is.
I don't know.
Miguel, make sure.
Your secrecy won't help you now.
I'm not lying to you.
I'll do anything to get out
of here, to be with you.
My Boss wants to help.
She says her husband
has connections.
She said she can ask him
to look into your case.
Please tell her, thank you.
I'm thinking about nothing
else right now
but your safety and Joey's
because you're important to me.
Elai messaged me, and she said
that you couldn't be reached.
And apparently,
you have a backlog again.
Well, Yvette, I just don't
have a signal where I went.
And where exactly is that?
You're always on the move,
but you're not with your team.
Do you have a girlfriend?
What? Hey!
I'm your sister.
You know, I miss times
like this, you know,
we're just talking about
anything under the sun.
Come on, come on.
Is she pretty?
Yvette, I'm not dating anyone.
But I'm helping someone
with a case.
That's it.
This is so good!
What is it called again?
It has tapa, and then
that's garlic rice...
that's the rice. And then egg,
the egg.
So it's tap-si-log.
- Tapsilog, right?
- Yes.
It's delicious.
Yes, right?
Failed!
No one from the people I've
asked has recognized her yet.
Well, it's still early.
We'll still go around.
- Okay, I'll just pay.
- Okay.
Wait. What's your diet?
How much, Miss?
So what do you like better?
Korean rice or Filipino rice?
Never mind.
Wait!
Hey, move over!
That's Golda's driver.
Are you okay?
Have you paid already?
It's a good thing I saw him
before they left.
It's a good thing we didn't ask
him about Golda,
or else we'd be caught.
Let's just follow him.
I'm sure she'll show us
where Golda is.
And what is she like?
Is she sweet?
Nice?
Wife material?
She's annoying.
Yvette, we always clash.
She's always hot-tempered,
and I'm the one who always gets
involved.
And her eyes, she'll give you
the intense look.
It's like you're always
being judged.
So grumpy.
You know what's so funny?
You never described
a woman this way.
Usually, all you say is,
okay and kind.
That's it, that's all.
Well, because she's not okay
or kind.
She drives me crazy, actually.
Usually, that's how it starts,
you know.
You fight and argue, and then,
eventually,
you exhaust the worst
of each other
until you see the best
of each other.
Yvette, we're not like that.
Not really.
We have no common ground,
not even a square inch.
Just wait.
There will come a moment,
you know.
A crack in the wall...
A look, then you'll suddenly
realize...
Why does this girl matter a lot?
This is it.
Looks like we're close.
(BACKGROUND SOUNDS)
Are they going to the carnival?
Come on, let's follow.
(BACKGROUND SOUNDS)
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Andrew, tell me the truth.
Are you working on an expose
that we don't know about?
I need to keep my distance.
If you're too close,
they will get suspicious again.
That's the M14 and AK-47.
Will you offer that to them,
too?
Exactly.
This is where Golda is hiding?
Wow. You're really good
at your job.
Lucky, I guess.
Are you mad at me?
I'm your best friend, right?
Wow. Clingy?
Fine, so what if I'm clingy?
What can you do? I love you!
Do you know the one they call
Godfather?
That's Vincent Alcala.
Be careful with him.
This is a big syndicate.